<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alt_F4</title>
    <link>https://www.altf4.space/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alt_F4</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Athul</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.altf4.space/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VMware VCP-NV 2022 Certified</title>
      <link>https://www.altf4.space/posts/3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.altf4.space/posts/3/</guid>
      <description>.center {text-align:center;}Finally I got the VMware VCP-NV 2022 Certification, taking the exam 2V0-41.20.
I came from 5+ years experience in virtualization area, working with VMware, Proxmox and so on.
Experience on vSphere environments is not a plus, but a mandatory requirement: a lot of questions cover topics not only related to NSX-T but also to vSphere (ESXi, vCenter, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death is nothing at all</title>
      <link>https://www.altf4.space/posts/2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.altf4.space/posts/2/</guid>
      <description>Death is nothing at all. It does not count.
I have only slipped away into the next room.
Nothing has happened.
Everything remains exactly as it was.
I am I, and you are you, and the old life that we lived so fondly together is untouched, unchanged.
Whatever we were to each other, that we are still.
Call me by the old familiar name.
Speak of me in the easy way which you always used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About </title>
      <link>https://www.altf4.space/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.altf4.space/about/</guid>
      <description>Francesco Racano  Telecommunication Engineer  NFV Engineer 7+ years experience working for Capgemini Engineering vSphere 7 (ESXi, vCenter, vCloud, NSX-T, vROPs)   Technology Geek  currently on W11 with WSL2  coming from Debian XFCE years     Trekking Lover Sport Enthusiast  Awards and Certifications:  VMware Certified Professional – Network Virtualization 2022 (VCP-NV) AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner VMware Certified Professional - Data Center Virtualization 2021 (VCP-DCV) Essential and Advanced Developer Certification Autopsy Digital Forensics Certification CCNA Master’s Degree - Telecommunication Engineering - Politecnico di Bari Degree - Telecommunication Engineering - Politecnico di Bari  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here we go</title>
      <link>https://www.altf4.space/posts/1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.altf4.space/posts/1/</guid>
      <description>Like closing a window, insert a space and starting again and again. A new start, fresh air. A soul has leaved us…I want to celebrate this with a new opened window.
altf4.space will be used to go indeep on everything related to technology, life hacks, thoughts, trekking, sports, nutritions and so on. So everything that sparke me a brain movements and life happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>